[{"answer": "Now how'd he figure that out", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "A sick horse?  What the hell..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Just wanted to let you know You're sitting in my chair", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yeah.  It's a fact", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Don't need to go heeled to get The bulge on a dub like you", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yeah.  It's a fact", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "And you must be my friend.  Look, Darling, Johnny my friend.  The Deadliest pistoleer since my friend, they say.  What do you Think, darling?  Should I hate him", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes, but there's just something About him.  Something around The eyes, I don't know, reminds me Of... me.  No.  I'm sure of it, I Hate him", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I couldn't help it, my friend.  I Looked at that woman and it was Just like somebody slapping me in The face.  I mean these people're Afraid to even walk down the Street and I'm trying to make Money off it like some kind of God damn vulture.  That's not me, That's somebody I don't even know", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "It's got nothin' to do with you, my friend.  It'", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend, isn't it?  Listen, you Seen a black stallion wit", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm not a lawman, I'm just a Private citizen getting' my Property bac", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Ain't our way.  We go all on one, One on all.  Fight one of us, you Fight us all.  That's the Cowboy way", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh, we ride for a brand all right.  This brand.  How 'bout you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "And how come you call yourselves Cowboys?  Cowhands ride for the brand", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " This brand", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh...  Now she's starting.  How do they know", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I have a better idea, let's run It out of them", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What's wrong", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I know, me too.  What should we do About it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Easy to fix.  my friend", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend... No, I'm gonna call you my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I don't know.  I'm all right", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Sure I'm sure.  What is this", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Not exactly..", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes, I know.  You are a good woman", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Not half as bad as I feel", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "my friend is my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "He's right, my friend.  my friend could Put five into you before you Could even get one into him", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "All right my friend, maybe you can. But you gotta die to do it. Understand?  You gotta die", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "A man like my friend's got a great Empty hole right through the Middle of him and no matter what He does he can't ever fill it.  He Can't kill enough or steal enough Or inflict enough pain to ever Fill it.  And it drives him mad. Sick mad.  Cold and dirty", "docId": "tomb_stone.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What does he want?  He wants revenge", "qsentId": 32}]